What's going on? Damn it!
怎麼回事 可惡
W-Who are you?
妳…妳是誰
I came to meet the Hero and his party.
我是來見蔚為話題的 勇者大人一行人
I didn't realize it was just a trio of dorks.
沒想到只是大呆瓜三人組
Her magic is really powerful.
那招魔法超強
She might even surpass Fred.
搞不好凌駕於弗雷德之上
Thank you for saving us.
謝謝妳替我們解圍
I will be the one to defeat the Demon Lord.
擊敗魔王的人將是我
You guys might as well go home and drink your mother's milk.
你們還是滾回家吸媽媽的奶吧
Why is it you again?
怎麼又是妳
Thank you for saving us, Yuria.
謝謝妳搭救 尤莉亞
Come a bit closer.
過來一點吧
You're cold, aren't you?
妳會冷吧
Although those enemies are demons, they are mostly just minions.
雖然是魔族 幾乎都是蝦兵蟹將
I was all geared up for nothing.
虧我還鼓足了幹勁
That's what I'm saying.
就是說啊
We will save you the next time, Yuria.
下次就換我們替妳解圍 尤莉亞
That guy's got a real attitude.
那傢伙態度真冷淡
You're not in a position to talk about her.
你哪有資格說人家
Didn't I tell you to go home?
不是叫你們滾回家嗎
And you dare say all demons are just minions.
還敢說魔族都是蝦兵蟹將
You guys didn't see it at all.
你們根本沒看出來
The opponents are getting tougher.
出現的對手越來越難纏
If I hadn't helped,
要不是我出手幫忙
you would have been killed.
你們早就葬身於此
This is my last advice.
這是最後的忠告
When the sun rises, you guys should just go home.
等天亮了 你們就乖乖回家去吧
Yuria,
尤莉亞
you don't have to be so mean.
別說那麼見外的話
We are companions now, aren't we?
我們已經是夥伴了吧
I don't need companions.
我不需要什麼夥伴
Why is she so angry?
那傢伙何必生氣
Just ignore her.
別管她了
I see.
原來如此
It's a shame to keep you in the human realm.
讓妳留在人界實在太可惜了
Would you like to be reincarnated as a demon?
想不想轉生為魔之眷屬
Spare me the joke.
這種玩笑就免了
My goal is to defeat the Demon Lord.
我的目標是打倒魔王
And I'm the only one who can do it.
而且這件事非我不可
Because you refuse to obey,
既然妳本人不肯服從
I will make your corpse serve me.
不妨使妳的屍體聽命於我
Yuria!
尤莉亞
You attacked a single woman, how despicable.
居然攻擊落單的女性 卑鄙無恥
This guy seems quite tough.
看來這傢伙相當難對付
I need to give it my all.
使出全力吧
(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《Lv1魔王與獨居廢勇者》
(Episode10: Leo vs. Fred)
(#10 雷奧vs弗雷德)
Do you think you can beat me with brute force,
以為能用蠻力硬碰硬贏我嗎
Fred?
弗雷德
He hit it.
砍中了
Chief.
長官
It brings back old memories.
真叫人懷念
Your healing spell has saved me
你那招復原咒語
numerous times in the past.
以前救了我無數次
But your way of fighting is quite reckless.
但這種戰鬥方式相當魯莽
Why did you choose to fight alone?
為什麼單槍匹馬應戰
I thought you would bring Max and the others.
還以為你會帶麥克斯他們一起來
Are they undead?
他們兩人是不死之身嗎
It seems like they're talking. Can you hear them?
好像在講什麼 收得到聲音嗎
It would be nice if they spoke a little louder.
如果他們講大聲一點就行
You've always been discreet.
你向來謹慎行事
Fighting me alone is not something you would do because it is reckless.
不可能做這種有勇無謀的傻事 和我近身單挑
I thought you had other considerations.
本來以為你另有考量
But it seems you really did come alone.
但看樣子你確實是一人前來
Are you here to die, Fred?
是來找死的嗎 弗雷德
You're overestimating yourself.
你未免太看得起自己了吧
Your companions put you on a pedestal, and you think you're a king.
同伴把你捧上天 自以為稱王
Has this made you forget your own strength?
連自己有幾分實力都搞不懂了嗎
I'm not a king.
我並不是什麼王
I know very well I'm not cut out for that.
我自己最清楚我不是那塊料
Nonsense.
廢話
You said I'm reckless, and I return those words to you.
你說我有勇無謀 這句話原封不動還你
This stupid situation was entirely your fault.
擅自搞出這檔蠢事
What? Republic Gamma?
什麼剛瑪共和國
Don't underestimate people!
少瞧不起人了
Of course, I understand. It's indeed stupid.
我當然明白 確實愚蠢
But…
不過…
When I was exiled to this 'Millennium Wilderness,'
當我被驅逐到 這片人稱"千年荒野"的土地時
there were subordinates willing to follow me,
有一群願意追隨我而來的部下
companions who admired me,
有一群願意景仰我的夥伴
and together we developed this land that even the kingdom had abandoned.
和我一同開拓 這片連王國都棄之不顧的土地
We all dug up the magical ore and the hot springs
大家都是抱著必死決心
with the determination to die.
才挖出魔礦脈與溫泉
The kingdom, however, offered no rewards and attempted to take everything.
王國卻不給任何回報 企圖奪走這一切
How should they live in the future, and how should they feel about it?
他們以後該如何過活 又該抱著什麼心情
Indeed.
是啊
This is utterly unreasonable.
這種事實在太不講理
But not getting rewards despite hard work is a common occurrence.
但是付出努力仍得不到回報 是常有的事
You should have realized your limits earlier.
應該早點認清自己有幾兩重
Whether it's you or those incompetent subordinates.
不管是你 或是那些無能部下
Do you think the kingdom will
難道你以為殺了我
recognize your independence if you kill me?
王國就會承認你們地位獨立嗎
The pointless war you started will never end.
你們挑起的無謂戰爭 永遠都不會結束
The war will definitely end. I will end it with my own hands.
肯定會結束 我將親手了結
Our voices can surely reach the citizens of the kingdom.
我們的聲音 一定也能傳達給王國國民
One day, they will be willing to listen.
他們總有一天會願意傾聽
Perhaps so.
也許是吧
You can keep fighting all you want.
隨便你怎麼繼續死纏爛打
Your demands will surely be conveyed.
聲音一定能傳達出去吧
I'm sure it'll end well someday.
總有一天肯定會圓滿收場吧
Assuming that everyone in the world is like you,
前提是全世界的人都像你一樣
mentally and physically healthy, upright and honest.
身心健全又正直老實
LIVE, THE KINGDOM ATTACKS THE REPUBLIC GAMMA LIVE
(實況轉播 王國進攻剛瑪共和國！直播中！)
As expected of Leo and Fred.
不愧是雷奧和弗雷德
Their abilities have not deteriorated in the ten years since.
與十年前相比 身手絲毫沒退步
The battle is fierce.
戰況激烈
If this continues, their bodies won't hold up.
再這樣下去他們的身體會撐不住
Aren't you watching?
你不看嗎
I'm not interested.
沒興趣
This isn't the time for you to be snide.
現在不是說風涼話的時候
They're your companions.
他們是你的夥伴
This is basically mutual slaughter.
這根本是在互相殘殺了
It's not something you can ignore with a "not interested."
怎麼能以一句"沒興趣"就了事
Are you just going to watch your companions die?
你是想眼睜睜等夥伴去死嗎
Speak up, hero.
說話啊 勇者
Shut up.
吵死人了
What else can I do?
不然你要我怎麼辦
What can I do if I go there?
我去那裡能幹嘛
Which side should I stand on?
我要站在哪一邊才對
Tell me.
說啊
This is about me killing
這是叫我去殺了雷奧或弗雷德
Leo or Fred, isn't it?
不是嗎
Are you trying to force me to make a choice?
你是想逼我做出選擇嗎
Is that so?
是嗎
What a pity, Max.
實在遺憾 麥克斯
In that case, do as you wish.
既然如此 那就隨便你
I will leave you be.
朕不認你這個人了
Farewell.
永別了
That's why I said you're too honest.
所以我才說你過於老實
You bastard.
你這個混蛋
This guy is…
這傢伙是…
W-What?
什…什麼
What happened?
發生什麼事
It hurts like hell.
痛死了
The camera…
攝影機…
Found it.
找到了
Long time no see, foolish humans.
好久不見 愚蠢的人類們
What?
什麼
How did she suddenly appear?
怎麼突然冒出來
I originally came to see your stupid faces in peace.
原本是來瞧瞧你們安於和平的蠢臉
Then I ran into a boring human fight.
竟然正好碰上人類之間的無聊鬥爭
This is so pleasant.
簡直太愉快了
Come on, humans.
來吧 人類們
Recall your past fears.
回想起過往的恐懼
At this moment,
朕在此時此刻
I officially announce the full resurrection of the Demon Lord.
正式宣布魔王完全復活
How cute.
好可愛
That guy.
那傢伙
What is he doing?
他在幹什麼
What's up with that brat?
那個小鬼頭是怎樣
Did he mention something about Demon Lord?
他是不是提到什麼魔王
Who knows, quickly tell him to get out of the way.
誰知道啊 快叫他閃邊去
How can we tell him to get out of the way from here?
從這邊要怎麼叫他
Don't mess with the drone.
不要亂碰無人機
That demon is…
那個魔族是…
Do you know who he is?
你知道他是誰嗎
He was the demon by his side the day I saw Max.
是我見到麥克斯那天 在他旁邊的魔族
What are you saying?
你說什麼
I know Max has been hanging out with demons recently,
我知道麥克斯最近跟魔族廝混
but this is the first time I've seen that demon.
但我還是第一次見到那個魔族
What the hell is he thinking?
那傢伙到底在想什麼
Demon Lord?
魔王…
First, to celebrate my resurrection,
首先是慶祝朕復活
I'm going to kill the hero's companions in a bloody mess.
把那兩個勇者夥伴殺得血肉模糊
You, who are wounded all over, are not my adversaries.
渾身負傷的你們 完全不是朕的對手
Sink into my darkness, Leo, Fred.
沉沒於朕的黑暗之中吧 雷奧 弗雷德
W-Wait. Seriously?
等…等等 騙人的吧
Take this!
接招吧
It seems we have to interrupt.
被旁人打斷了
Yeah.
是啊
How is that possible?
怎麼可能
What do you think, Fred?
你覺得呢 弗雷德
It seems familiar, is he really…
似乎似曾相識 莫非真是…
When the hero is not present,
勇者不在場
you shamelessly begin infighting.
你們就恬不知恥起內鬨
It's simply not worth fearing.
簡直不足為懼
Hero Max, you see everything, don't you?
勇者麥克斯 你都看到了吧
What are you doing?
究竟在做什麼
If you don't come over,
再不過來
you will truly lose everything this time.
你這次是真的會失去一切
If you don't want to watch your friends die,
如果你不想看朋友送死
hurry up and come over.
就不要拖拖拉拉的 快點過來
Let's do it again, Max.
再一次挺身而出吧 麥克斯
It seems like one more thing I have to ask Max about.
又多了一件 需要向麥克斯問清楚的事
Then let's finish this first.
那就先做個了斷吧
In case someone else interferes.
以防又有人插手攪局
Damn it.
該死的
Everyone is doing this to me.
每個傢伙都一個樣
I don't care anymore.
不管了
I really don't care anymore.
再也不管了
Whatever.
隨便
Whatever works.
管他怎樣都行啦
Testing.
測試…
I am not sure if the audience is getting this.
正在觀看直播的各位觀眾 是否看得出來
Fred and Leo have been fighting fiercely since just now.
弗雷德與雷奧 從剛才開始激烈戰鬥不斷
The kingdom and republic's fate depends on their fight.
這兩人誰輸誰贏 想必掌握了王國與共和國的命運
Which side will triumph over
高超絕技以及魔法反擊
superb skills and magical counterattacks?
究竟會是哪一方獲勝
Someone commented that you're noisy.
有人留言嫌妳吵
Okay.
好
Let's go.
出發吧
The chain came loose.
原來鍊條鬆掉了
It's really not good.
果然沒好事
It's a pain in the ass, and it makes my hands dirty.
有夠麻煩 還會弄髒手
I might as well not go.
說真的 乾脆別去了
Oh man.
唉唷
Geez.
真是的
What is that?
什麼東西
Look out!
閃開
The traffic is congested, the road is narrow,
塞車塞到天邊 路還這麼窄
and they still insist that "bicycles must ride in the lane."
還說什麼"自行車需行駛於車道"
The lane should then be
那就把車道重新整頓一下
reorganized to allow bicycles to pass!
好讓自行車通過
Well then, you should be prepared to die.
那麼 你也該做好覺悟去死了吧
Yeah, but…
是啊 不過…
You're prepared too, right?
你當然也做好覺悟了吧
Chief, please.
長官 求求您
Let's stop here.
就此收手吧
What's wrong?
怎麼了
Don't block the way!
別擋路
Die, Leo!
去死吧 雷奧
Bring it on, Fred!
放馬過來 弗雷德
What a surprise, I've run out of moves.
真是令人吃驚 彈藥耗盡了
We've got him on the ropes.
逼到絕境了
Just give up.
你還是死心吧
You are so hurt, and yet you want to fight me.
傷成那樣 還想跟我打
Even when death is near, you keep talking big…
還敢在那邊放話 死到臨頭還…
I'm looking forward to our next meeting.
很期待下一次見面
Damn it, he escaped.
可惡 被他逃了
Are you okay, Yuria?
還好嗎 尤莉亞
Thank goodness you're safe.
幸好妳平安無事
Why did you save me?
為什麼要救我
Because you're a valuable force to be reckoned with.
因為妳是利害關係一致的珍貴戰力
We can't just watch you die for nothing.
可不能眼睜睜看著妳白白死去
Do you know what this is called?
妳知道這叫做什麼嗎
It's called "companionship."
就是"夥伴"
Alright, let's go.
好了 出發吧